举起手来 远离无线电
Hands up! Move away from the radio.
我们没损坏任何东西
No harm's been done.
你们被逮捕了
You're under arrest.
未经授权使用政府设施
Unauthorized use of government property.
行尸走肉 前情提要
Previously, on "The Walking Dead"...
把他们放了 不管如何
Let them go. You'll have to pay
你们最终会为自己的行为付出代价
for what you've done, one way or another.
这个地方有看上去那么好吗
Is this place really as good as it seems?
- 好多了 - 在这里我可以为其他人
- Better. - If I wanted to get help
寻求帮助吗
for people, I could do that here?
只要你遵守规则
As long as you follow the rules.
不对 我们漏了什么
No, we're missing something.
可能他们从后面逃跑了
Maybe they went out the back.
我可以去追他们
I can track 'em.
等等
Hold on.
和你说了
Told ya.
等等
Wait.
休息一下 我们马上就到了
Take a minute, then we're almost there.
还有三英里
About three miles out.
你认真的吗
You can't be serious.
达里尔刚才还让我们回家
Daryl just told us to go home.
我没听见
I didn't hear that.
他是在暗示
Well, I think he was being subtle.
他说他们有很多哨兵
He said they were armed with lookouts.
达里尔知道我不会退缩的
And Daryl knows I would never turn back.
你怎么走下去 玛姬
How're you gonna keep going, Maggie, huh?
有什么武器
With what army?
Gabe 帮我说下话
Come on, Gabe, back me up here.
我们的人要饿死了
Our people are about to starve.
我不会空手而归的
I'm not going back to my family having failed.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
起码承认你要求我们...
At least admit what you're asking of us...
为了什么 一袋豆子去冒生命危险吗
walking to our deaths for what, a sack of beans?
如果你更想保护自己
If you're more interested in saving yourself
而不是保护社区里的人
than protecting the people back home,
你可以走了
you can go.
我们不需要你
We don't need you.
我们都知道这不是真的
We both know that's not true.
好吧 这样
Alright, tell you what.
你在牧师面前...
You make me a promise...
保证我一件事...
in front of the goddamn preacher...
我就不走
and I will stick around.
保证什么
Promise you what?
我这次帮你
I do this for you,
我们就扯平了
and we're even, we are good.
我就不用一直担惊受怕了
I don't have to keep looking over my shoulder.
我们永远都不会扯平
We will never be even.
那你就会少一名
Then you are gonna be down a soldier
你急需的队员
that you desperately need.
你自己决定
Your call.
你会相信我的承诺吗
You'd take a promise from me?
真的吗
Really?
真的 谁不会呢
Yeah. Who wouldn't?
我觉得你是言而有信的人
I'm assuming you are a woman of your word.
我也一直都信守承诺
I've always been a man of mine.
怎么了
What is it?
是他妹妹最好的朋友
It's his sister's best friend.
Teresa
Teresa.
她只是个孩子
She was just a kid.
我们要找到他们
We have to get them.
所有人
All of them.
嘿
Hey.
你们也知道Blackbeard吗
Y'all know Blackbeard, too?
等等
Wait.
你觉得我们还能找到更多吗
Think we can find more?
你做的很好
You're doing great.
一般吧 没有很好
I'm doing okay, not great.
在评价自己之前
The timeline since this was last
要考虑这件事作为你每天的
an essential activity in your daily routine
基本必要活动
and the necessity for it
是多久以前了
should be factors in your self-judgment.
军队会为我们做这些
The military does this for us.
已经很久不需要我来做了
It's been so long since I've had to.
但这个不像骑单车
It's not like riding a bicycle, turns out.
你还是会忘了怎么做
You do forget.
那是敬业的小脑
That's the good ol' cerebellum
在保护你免受痛苦回忆的打扰
protecting you from unpleasant memories.
我记得那些美好的东西
I remember the good stuff.
斯蒂芬妮 我要问下
Stephanie, I... I have to ask.
你认识霍恩斯比很久了吗
You've known Hornsby a long time?
挺久了 怎么了
Pretty long, why?
他能解决我们做的...
Is he capable of taking care of our...
违法事迹吗
transgressions?
换句话说
In other words,
做完这些劳工 我们会被放出去吗
will all this labor truly lead to our freedom?
如果他说会 那就会
If he says it will, it will.
兰斯有他自己的做事规矩
Lance has his own way of doing things.
但你可以信任他
But you can trust him.
你会知道的
You'll see.
让我来
Whoa. Let me take over.
- 我能搞定 - 我能帮忙 没事
- I got this. - I can help, it's fine.
- 不 有事 - 会没事的
- No, it's not! - It will be.
西结王
Ezekiel!
怎么了
What?
我爱你 但你要给我点空间
I love you, but you got to give me space, man.
你能把这些处理了吗
Can you just clear these?
天啊
God!
我把剩下的解决了
Think I got the last of them.
- 你没事吧 - 嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
没事
Fine.
对不起 我不是故意要发火的
Sorry, I didn't mean to snap at you.
只是那里面太挤了
It's just so cramped in there.
没事没事
Nah, it's cool.
西结王 我能帮你什么吗
Ezekiel, what can I do?
有... 有些灰尘
It's... It's dusty.
就是因为这个
I'm sure that's it.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
需要帮忙清理你们的区域吗
Y'all need help clearing your area?
Steph 我们还要在这里做多久
Steph, how much longer we got to do this?
已经好几天了
It's been days.
可能还要几天吧我猜
Uh, a couple more, I guess.
他撑不了几天了
He won't make it a few more days.
我没事
I'm fine.
不 你需要见医生
No, you need to see a doctor.
我不会留你一个人在这里干活的
I'm not gonna leave you alone to work out here.
别傻了
Don't be stupid!
我就这么说了
Yeah, I said it.
他们这里有真正的医院
They got real hospitals and shit here.
你能帮忙吗
Can you make that happen?
嗯 我现在就去找霍恩斯比先生
Uh, yeah, I'll talk to Mr. Hornsby right now.
谢谢 感激不尽
Thank you. We are much obliged.
如果这变成我们要用劳工来偿还的另一个债务
If this becomes another debt we have to work off...
我从来不怕干苦活
Never been afraid of hard work.
我可不喜欢朋友因为固执死去
Kinda anti friends who die from stubbornness.
默瑟 这离那些下贱的人
Mercer, this is way too close to
工作的地方也太近了吧
where the nasties are working.
这味道太... 恶心了
The smell is... revolting.
这人是谁啊
Who the hell was that?
我们的招募人员对你印象非常深刻
Our recruiters were incredibly impressed with you.
是吗
Were they?
我... 我以为他们觉得我很难搞
I... I thought maybe they found me difficult.
我们预料到你这种家庭背景的人
Well, we expect a person with your pedigree
要求会比较高
to have high standards.
在这里是这样的
We certainly do at State.
米尔顿女士对她的哈佛校友们
Well, Ms. Milton has great affection
非常有感情
for her fellow Harvard grads.
帮你找到一个职位完全没有问题
Should be no trouble finding a position for you.
我很乐意用工作去支付你们对我社区的援助
I'm happy to work to pay for the aid for my community,
但我不会一直在这里的
but I'm not staying here permanently.
我先把这个说清楚了
I just want to make that clear.
可能你见了米尔顿女士后会改变主意
After you meet Ms. Milton, you might reconsider.
我还是想先见我的朋友们
I'd rather see my friends.
有人能带我去
Actually, can somebody take me to where
他们工作的地方吗
they're working, please?
他们触犯了法律
They broke the law.
霍恩斯比先生在他们完成惩罚后
Mr. Hornsby has arranged for their release
会放他们出来的
with a fine that they're repaying.
什么
What?
嗯 他们应该在为以后的开发区
Yeah, I believe they're clearing buildings
清扫建筑
for future development.
具体是清扫什么
Clearing them of what, exactly?
行尸们
The dead.
所以他们被安排去清理行尸
Okay, so they're assigned to clear walkers
几天 还是几周
for days, weeks?